[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mitt Romney"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "I mean in the general context of the whole race, are we nearing the tipping point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Yes, I think it's a very impressive night for Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Republican Party"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Gloria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "You know, here's the problem for the Republican Party.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "I mean if he's the guy with the money, the infrastructure, the drive, and he can present a good case to beat Barack Obama, and the economy is his area of special -- specialty, which is what it's going to be fought over, why does it matter if a field of diehard conservatives don't really love him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ":", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Well, Piers, it does matter, but it's not the only thing that matters.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "How does Mitt Romney, if he wins the nomination, make his own party and the vote that comes with it love him enough to drive Barack Obama out of the White House?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "I think it's about hate, not love.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Governor Romney"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "How significant do you guys think tonight is for your campaign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Well, it's 21 states now, Piers, that Governor Romney has won.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April of 2011"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "I mean do you accept that your campaign tonight seem to be realigning itself back to where it began?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, I think we've stayed on jobs and the economy from the very beginning of this campaign back in April of 2011.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Is it time for at least some of the contestants here left in the Republican race to pull out, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, that's a personal decision.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Illinois"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "What will he do about his areas of weakness now to really cement this nomination?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, I think one of the interesting data points coming out of the Illinois exit polls is that Mitt Romney won among those people who said he understands the problems of average Americans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Well, given you're all in so much good moods over there at the Romney camp, how about giving me your man for another interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "RP", "VBG", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "What are your thoughts after tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Thank you for having me, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Is it time for some of the others, not necessarily your man, but some of them to drop out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Well, let me put it this way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "RABENDER: Well now I think what it really is is Rick is an authentic candidate who doesn't use a teleprompter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "-- to get himself over the line?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Romney has to win almost half of all of the delegates, as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["LSU"], "LOCATION": ["Baton Rouge"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "How do you respond to that heat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, I'm sitting here in Baton Rouge which is a few miles away from LSU.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Where is the love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "I mean, it's just not there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "I mean, to me, whoever wins the nomination has got to be well-funded enough to take on a rampant president, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "No, that's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Santorum"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "I mean it's completely unthinkable that one of these guys could yet make another stunning comeback?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "For me, it's too early to call Santorum out because we still have a few more states to go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "He's lost a bit of the surge, hasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I think he's lost a lot of momentum.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "You want to keep hitting the stuff that you're good at, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120320pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "How are you going to get other maybe Republicans actually to come out and fancy him, too, with the same ardent fervor that you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Well, Piers, first of all, I don't think it even matters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]